Richard Hodgson

Curriculum Vitae

Personal Details

Full name Date of Birth Nationality Richard Anthony Hodgson

8th May 1984 British Citizen

Permanent Address

11 Rushey Gill Brandon Durham County Durham DH7 8BL

Qualifications

Qualification	Subject	Grade
GCSE	English Language English Literature Mathematics Double Award Science Drama Graphic Products German Art	B C CC B C D
BTEC National Diploma	Computer Studies	2 Distinctions2 Merits4 Passes
Keyskills	Application of Number Information Technology	Pass Pass
ECDL		Pass
Degree (BSc.)	Web Development	Second Class Honours (2 nd Division)

Employment History

August 2004 ~ September 2005

Full-time Employment as Web Developer DfES Pathfinder Project - Fit4Employment (Placement)

September 2005 ~ June 2006

Consultancy (Web focused / Intranet orientated)
Durham Community Business College

July 2006 ~ Present

Full-time Employment as Web Developer Durham Federation (Durham Community Business College & Fyndoune Community College)

References

Mrs A Lakey (Head Teacher)

Durham Community Business College Bracken Court Ushaw Moor Durham

DH7 7NG

Mr P Robinson

5 Thornbury Rise Darlington

DL3 9NE

Personal Statement

In general, I have always found computing an easy subject to comprehend. From the age of 10 onwards, I have demonstrated that my one of my main strengths is analysing and understanding systems, in all shapes and form. Computing is a subject which I find self motivating, especially in the field of web related technologies.

I have been learning about making websites for nearly 10 years now. It has grown from an idle hobby to a marketable skill; one that I hope can make a good contribution back to the industry.

When I'm not planning, developing or talking about websites, I enjoy watching anything by Simon Pegg, attempting to mix on my record decks or simply relaxing and socialising with friends.

I have also be known to juggle, ride my bike, go paint balling, cook and build complex multi-amplifier sound systems.

Further information and examples of my work can be found at http://www.rhodgson.co.uk.